hey guys what's up Rob mods here wanted
to bring you some more gameplay today
this is actually towards the end of my
session so it's gonna be a little bit
different than what it has been the last
couple of times I actually just finished
running through about 900 mil of the net
worth and so one of the topics I
actually want to cover right now is shop
layout and upgrades a lot of people have
been asking me especially with endgame
what does it actually look like how do
you balance bins and racks and just kind
of how I do things towards really late
late game so I'm just gonna explain that
really quick before I head off to bed so
I've talked about it a little bit before
but I've I have a couple of setups so
right now when I have all of my bins out
all of my tier 1 resources are over 600
all my tier 2 resources are almost at
200 and then I've got a lot of two or
three resources as well but when I'm
wanting to sell like I have for the past
couple of hours I'm wanting a lot more
energy than that gives and of course
having this many bins out doesn't do
anything if you're using all the
resources right away it doesn't do
anything so let me show you what this
looks like for me to switch everything
over of course there's no button to do
this automatically so here we go so
right now I'm just pressing store and
putting everything away so for this I
use two chests rather than four because
when you have all those extra racks out
it actually increases your storage for
each space that the rack can hold like
four items so you don't actually need as
much storage and it gives me an extra
couple hundred energy as well so I know
this is a little bit painful of a
process but it's worthwhile
wow this is weird I've never done this
okay so the game crashed there but it's
all good or back so I just switched out
almost all of my bins for racks so as
you can see I'm at 7000 energy right now
exactly and so this for me is the most
ideal setup where I can still craft so
I'm still making money crafting items
obviously I have to pay a lot more
attention because not as much the the
maximum isn't as high so I can't you
know login and craft twelve items I can
login and craft four items so I have to
pay a lot more attention but I think it
makes a lot more sense to do it that way
so if I small talk can I get 700 energy
I can discount it to your six item and
surcharge a tier nine item immediately
and then I just have one of each bin out
so this is what most top players are
gonna have this is what their shop is
gonna look like they're gonna have the
same amount of energy all of these are
max so this is basically a max shop if
you're still crafting right now but
there's another option that I've been
really debating and I'd love to hear
your input on it and just see what you
think so
I've been thinking if I store all of my
bins what would it look like if I went
entirely racks and I had 800 energy and
I could just small talk and surcharge a
tier 9 without discounting anything
would that help me out would that speed
things up would that be more profitable
or does it make sense to still be
crafting constantly so that's why I've
been making these mannequins I haven't
upgraded them to 15 yet just because
it's a lot more money and gems to do
that I may do it later I haven't fully
decided yet but I've just been doing
this because it's cheap and you know I'm
able to try things out so also we'll buy
our last one right now perfect there it
is
so let's upgrade this guy I wanted to
mention this as well so when you upgrade
this it's gonna start you know with with
the full timer there your guild can help
you up to five times and that'll
decrease the timer to half a lot of the
time once I hit like level nine or level
ten I'll just wait until five of my
guild members have helped me out and
then I I rushed the rest of that with
gems that's really the only way you're
gonna get max with anything because it
takes so long to to upgrade and with
this many you know it's just not gonna
work so my energy now is at 73 hundred
if all of these are max at level 15 I
believe that your energy can get above
8,000 and especially if I took out these
two chests I couldn't carry a chance or
buy more components but I wouldn't
really need to if I have you know enough
items that are ready to sell and I could
probably get up to like 8200 energy or
something like that so I could small
talk and sell a tier 9 instantly without
discounting anything so that might be
more profitable because I don't have to
buy fodder or anything and it might be a
little bit faster with selling items
like if we just small talk here
basically anytime I get a successful
small talk I'm gonna be able to sell
something like look at this it's just
crazy every time it's successful I'm
able to get rid of one over and over and
over again this is crazy luck like this
never happens but like look at this how
many items don't I just sell like the
laws and it crashed again so I guess
QuickTime just doesn't like me but it's
all good know where he's we're almost
done anyway so yeah that was crazy
basically every item just sold it's one
small talk and the items gone it's
amazing so like small talk buy the item
and I've got enough to get another one
like this is what it looks like when you
have enough energy you can sell so
quickly that it might even be more
profitable for me to do it this way then
actually crafting items if I'm making
you know 100k profit per item that I'm
selling that might be faster than
crafting
but then of course there's no chance for
Legendary's and stuff so it might not
actually be but if you're super super
super endgame and your only goal is to
get net worth up as fast as possible
then having 8k energy being able to
surcharge anything as long as you small
talk successfully that's going to be
your fastest way so that might you know
be an option when I hit really late-game
and I don't care how much gold I have I
just want to make a net worth as fast as
possible so comment let me know what you
think three options really one is having
lots of bins out so that you can create
I can craft throughout the day option
two is having one of each bin out so
that I can still craft while I'm selling
with 7k energy and option three is
something that I haven't maxed out yet
but having 8000 or 8200 energy to just
surcharge immediately to be able to sell
everything fast so I don't know we'll
see so there we go level 2 and the next
one takes an hour half that is half an
hour so we'll get that up to level 3
anyways the last thing I want to mention
and this is a question that I had and
this has to do with shop layout as well
is is it better to have a closed layout
like this or an open layout where they
can access everything honestly I think
it's totally up to you the point of this
is that the customers don't have to walk
as far and you can you can limit the
amount of shelves that they can hit so
they're only gonna choose items that
they can access so it makes it a little
bit more controllable and they choose
items faster so they're not walking
around wasting time if there's too many
customers in a really small space it'll
say to many customers and they'll leave
so that's not ideal but it's kind of up
to you whatever you prefer until I got
to late-game I had an open concept the
entire time and I liked it just cuz it
looked better and I didn't really care
about how fast customers chose an item
so you know it's totally up to you
whatever you want to do it's kind of
personal preference some people like it
some people don't but for me when I'm
just focusing on net worth and want to
get through customers as quick as
possible you know this works for me so
it's totally up to you hopefully this
gives you something to think about and I
to hear your comments on which scenario
one two or three that you prefer and
what you'll be going with when you hit
endgame as well so anyway thanks for
watching guys hope you enjoyed talk to
you soon